HERE Joint Executive Board Files on Microfilm. 6199/012 mf
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Spokane, WA., 8 (Reel 21)
  Beginning at location 1344.
- Spokane, WA. Jurisdiction., 9 (Reel 21)
  Beginning at location 1345.
- Spokane, WA., 1963-1979; 10 (Reel 21)
  Beginning at location 1444.
- Spokane, WA. World's Fair., 11 (Reel 21)
  Beginning at location 1690.
- Spokane, WA. Audit Reports (Quarterly)., 12 (Reel 21)
  Beginning at location 1782.
- Spokane, WA. International Audit Reports., 13 (Reel 21)
  Beginning at location 1914.
- Tacoma, WA., 14 (Reel 21)
  Beginning at location 2041.
- Tacoma, WA. Audit Reports (Quarterly)., 15 (Reel 21)
  Beginning at location 2042.
- Yakima, WA., 16 (Reel 21)
  Beginning at location 2139.
- Yakima, WA. Audit Reports (Quarterly)., 17 (Reel 21)
  Beginning at location 2140.
- Cheyenne, WY., 18 (Reel 21)
  Beginning at location 2208.
- Cheyenne, WY. Audit Reports (Quarterly)., 19 (Reel 21)
  Beginning at location 2209.
- Anchorage, AK., 1 (Reel 22)
- Anchorage, AK. Correspondence., 1953-1981; 2 (Reel 22)
- Anchorage, AK. Emergency Disaster Fund., 1964; 3 (Reel 22)
- Anchorage, AK. Audit Reports (Quarterly)., 4 (Reel 22)
  Beginning at location 0609.
- Anchorage, AK. International Audit Reports., 5 (Reel 22)
  Beginning at location 0769.
- Chicago, IL. J.C.D.C.E., 6 (Reel 22)
  Beginning at location 0811.
- Chicago, IL. Correspondence., 1980-1981; 7 (Reel 22)
  Beginning at location 0812.
- Chicago, IL. Audit Reports (Quarterly)., 8 (Reel 22)
  Beginning at location 0911.
- Chicago, IL. International Audit Reports. (J.C.D.C.E.)., 9 (Reel 22)
  Beginning at location 1214.
- Chicago, IL. (continued)., 1 (Reel 23)
- Chicago, IL. Correspondence., 1943-1954; 2 (Reel 23)
- Chicago, IL. Minutes., 1948-1949; 3 (Reel 23)
  Beginning at location 1689.
- Chicago, IL. Crime Commission and Employee Association. Correspondence., 1951; 4 (Reel 23)
  Beginning at location 2040.
- Chicago, IL. Organizing Staff Reports., 1952; 5 (Reel 23)
  Beginning at location 2064.
- Chicago, IL. (continued)., 1 (Reel 24)
- Chicago, IL. Edgewater Beach Hotel., 1953-1954; 2 (Reel 24)
- Chicago, IL. Marquis Restaurants., 1954; 3 (Reel 24)
  Beginning at location 0116.
- Chicago, IL. Correspondence., 1955-1959; 4 (Reel 24)
  Beginning at location 0134.
- Chicago, IL. Minutes., 1958; 5 (Reel 24)
  Beginning at location 1625.
- Chicago, IL. Trusteeship., 1958-1960; 6 (Reel 24)
  Beginning at location 2074.
- Chicago, IL. (continued)., 1 (Reel 25)
- Chicago, IL. Correspondence., 1960; 2 (Reel 25)
- Chicago, IL. Correspondence., 1961; 3 (Reel 25)
  Beginning at location 0384.
- Chicago, IL. Correspondence., 1962; 4 (Reel 25)
  Beginning at location 0849.
- Chicago, IL. Correspondence., 1963; 5 (Reel 25)
  Beginning at location 1223.
- Chicago, IL. Correspondence., 1964; 6 (Reel 25)
  Beginning at location 1548.
- Chicago, IL. Correspondence., 1965; 7 (Reel 25)
  Beginning at location 1758.
- Chicago, IL. Correspondence., 1966-1967; 8 (Reel 25)
  Beginning at location 1979.
- Chicago, IL. (continued)., 1 (Reel 26)
- Chicago, IL. Correspondence., 1928-1969; 2 (Reel 26)
- Chicago, IL. Correspondence., 1970-1981; 3 (Reel 26)
  Beginning at location 0393.
- Chicago, IL. Sears Tower Restaurants Recognition Argeement., 1973; 4 (Reel 26)
  Beginning at location 1217.
- Chicago, IL. Audit Reports (Quarterly), 5 (Reel 26)
  Beginning at location 1222.
- Chicago, IL. International Audit Reports., 6 (Reel 26)
  Beginning at location 1470.
- International Falls, MN., 7 (Reel 26)
  Beginning at location 1585.
- International Falls, MN., 1959-1981; 8 (Reel 26)
  Beginning at location 1856.
- International Falls, MN., 1959-1967; 9 (Reel 26)
  Beginning at location 1602.
- Las Vegas, NV., 10 (Reel 26)
  Beginning at location 1627.
- Las Vegas, NV., 1942-1981; 11 (Reel 26)
  Beginning at location 1628.
- Las Vegas, NV., 12 (Reel 26)
  Beginning at location 2134.
- Las Vegas, NV., 13 (Reel 26)
  Beginning at location 2353.